Shawty I’m hot
Imma hit that like your man can not
I got the internet why you want my hotspot
They never pop off watch out I’m the god
Woah woah woah woah shawty I’m hot
Imma hit that like your man can not
I got the internet why you want my hotspot
They never pop off watch out I’m the god
Bro shut the f*ck up or Imma f*ck up your day
អានេះមិនមែនជាគ្នាយើងវាជាគ្នាគេ
Don’t hit ma phone get the f*ck out ma way
I don’t need no fake friend
I got ninety k in ma hands
Hundred bands, say again
What’s your name
Tell your friends you are lame
God damn same same difference
Suck my d*ck my ការ៉េម
Take ma tip play ma game
I’m the king kiss the ring
Put the lil boy in the dirt
f*ck ur b*tch, f*ck ur mama, f*ck what u heard
Tryna be me but u dumb as f*ck
Broke ass homie why your life so stuck
ជីវិតវាមិនអស្ចារ្យ តែវាគិតតែអួត
ដាក់ហែងនៅ១កន្លែងអោយហែងឆ្កួតនឹងអំនួត
វាគិតថាខ្លួនវាមានតែមួយនៅលើលោក
កង្កែបក្នុងអណ្ដូង ចង់ធ្វើស្ដេចនៅលើគោក
Shawty I’m hot
Imma hit that like your man can not
I got the internet why you want my hotspot
They never pop off watch out I'm the god
Woah woah shawty I’m hot
Imma hit that like your man can not
I got the internet why you want my hotspot
They never pop off watch out I'm the god
Woah, b*tch I'm good and I'm bad
I'm good with the flow
But I'm bad in the bed
Come to my condo if your kitty wet
ងូតទឹកឲ្យហើយ ហើយអង្គុយចាំមួយភ្លែត
I just wanna smoke before I hit (why)
Cause I’m the man who she needs (woah)
Cool outside but I'm hot
ព្រាយក្នុងលលាដ៏ កំពុងតែសុំចុះចត
Get off ma dick I just wanna headshot
ចេញទៅអោយឆ្ងាយនៅទីនេះគ្មានចំណត
ឃើញខ្ញុំនៅក្រៅ but we can’t hang out
មុខមាត់មិនសូវនិយាយ តែសម្ដីមិនបាច់ប្រដៅ
B*tch I’m a player មើលធ្លុះដល់ក្រយ៉ៅ
Real talk កុំក្អក ប្រយ័ត្នតែហ្មងសៅ
Talk to me និយាយអោយចំ point
Smoke with me no u can't get a joint
F*ck with me no your bitch so ត្រលាន់
Number one on top I got a lot of មាន់
ក្ដីស្រម៉ៃតាំងពីតូច I gotta blow my sh*t up
ដួល again ងើប again ខ្ញុំកំពុងតែប្រញាប់
ដៃទាំង២មមាញឹក ជើងទាំងពីរក៏ស្វាហាប់
លោតផ្លោះបោះជំហ៊ាន ខ្ញុំកំពុងតែហោះស្រាប់
ឈប់សំរាកនឹងគេដែរក៏ប៉ុន្ដែ មិនដែលបានដល់ស្អែក
វាគ្មានថ្ងៃអាទិត្យណាសំរាប់ខ្ញុំ វាជារឿងពិតមិនអាចប្រកែក
ត្រូវតែងើបក្ដិតទាន់ចិត្តនៅក្ដៅ
ស្អីធ្វើមិនកើតត្រូវទុកមួយឡែក បញ្ចេញកំលាំង
ដូចចេញទៅច្បាំងតាំងចិត្តអោយខ្លាំងរឹងដូចជាដែក f*ck
M******* ត្រូវធ្វើឲ្យបាន
កុំខ្វល់នឹងសម្ដីពួកតិរច្ឆាន
Imma f*cking dope មានមួយចានសុីមួយចាន
ដើរទៅមុខកុំអស់សង្ឃឹមពួកអានឹងវាមិនប៉ុន្មាន
Aye នេះគឺជាផ្លូវដែលត្រូវទៅ
គេតម្រូវអោយយើងចាប់កាន់សៀវភៅ
មើលអោយជាក់ញាក់ចិញ្ចើម
អ្នកត្រៀមខ្លួនហើយឬនៅ
ត្រៀមខ្លួនហើយឬនៅ
សួរថាត្រៀមហើយឬនៅ
បើសិននៅត្រូវតែទៅ
Woah woah woah shawty I’m hot
Imma hit that like your man can not
I got the internet why you want my hotspot
They never pop off watch out I'm the god
Woah Woah, Shawty I’m hot
Imma hit that like your man can not
I got the internet why you want my hotspot
They never pop off watch out I'm the god
Shawty I’m hot
Imma hit that like your man can not
I got the internet why you want my hotspot
They never pop off watch out I'm the god